[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Adventures in Babysitting, Chris and the kids are on the subway and are caught in the middle of a gang fight. Brad gets a knife stuck in his foot. How many stitches does he need?", "correct_answer": "1", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "3", "4"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which planet has been described as a sister planet to Earth?", "correct_answer": "Venus", "incorrect_answers": ["Mercury", "Saturn", "Mars"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which French artist is considered the founder of Fauvism?", "correct_answer": "Matisse", "incorrect_answers": ["Klee", "Monet", "Manet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following historical sites did not serve as a kind of observatory in the past?", "correct_answer": "The Great Sphinx of Giza, Egypt", "incorrect_answers": ["Abu Simbel, Egypt", "Stonehenge, Great Britain", "Kokino, Republic of Macedonia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Usually more than 10 million tourists visit three of these countries annually. Which is the odd one?", "correct_answer": "Belgium", "incorrect_answers": ["Poland", "Mexico", "Italy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name for a port used to connect peripheral devices (such as keyboards, mouses and digital cameras) to a computer?", "correct_answer": "USB", "incorrect_answers": ["Jack", "Floppy Drive", "BUS"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which cat is the advertising mascot for the 9Lives cat food?", "correct_answer": "Morris", "incorrect_answers": ["Garfield", "Odie", "Mermal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What amazing invention does Willy Wonka create in the 2005 movie Charlie and the Chocolate Factory?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Ice cream that doesnt melt", "Chewing gum for making giant balloons", "Chewing gum that does not lose its flavor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this card game, which is a predecessor to bridge, there is a trump suit, that can vary from hand to hand.", "correct_answer": "Whist", "incorrect_answers": ["Honeymoon Bridge", "Rummy", "Spades"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Muslims pray to Allah five times a day.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This North American animal is at the top of the food chain in the arctic region.", "correct_answer": "Polar Bear", "incorrect_answers": ["Walrus", "Arctic Fox", "Penguin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Steel Magnolias, during which holiday did Shelby announce she was expecting a baby?", "correct_answer": "Christmas", "incorrect_answers": ["Fourth of July", "Halloween", "Easter"]}]